{
  "base_model": "Jean-Baptiste/camembert-ner",
  "num_labels": 11,
  "labels": [
    "O",
    "B-PER",
    "I-PER",
    "B-LOC",
    "I-LOC",
    "B-ORG",
    "I-ORG",
    "B-DATE",
    "I-DATE",
    "B-TITLE",
    "I-TITLE"
  ],
  "bio_csv": "data\\ner\\bio_sample.csv",
  "num_sentences": 12,
  "num_tokens": 224,
  "alignment_policy": "first sub-token receives the BIO label; special and continuation tokens use -100",
  "seqeval_like_baseline": {
    "micro": {
      "precision": 1.0,
      "recall": 1.0,
      "f1": 1.0
    },
    "per_type": {
      "DATE": {
        "precision": 1.0,
        "recall": 1.0,
        "f1": 1.0
      },
      "LOC": {
        "precision": 1.0,
        "recall": 1.0,
        "f1": 1.0
      },
      "ORG": {
        "precision": 1.0,
        "recall": 1.0,
        "f1": 1.0
      },
      "PER": {
        "precision": 1.0,
        "recall": 1.0,
        "f1": 1.0
      },
      "TITLE": {
        "precision": 1.0,
        "recall": 1.0,
        "f1": 1.0
      }
    }
  },
  "next_step": "Fine-tune CamemBERT-LoRA on this CSV after expanding manual annotation."
}